var questions_C=[{
    "question":"Which of the following statements should be used to obtain a remainder after dividing 3.14 by 2.1 ?",
    "option1":"rem = 3.14 % 2.1;",
    "option2":"rem = modf(3.14, 2.1);",
    "option3":"rem = fmod(3.14, 2.1);",
    "option4":"Remainder cannot be obtain in floating point division",
    "answer":"3"

},{
    "question":"Which of the following special symbol allowed in a variable name?",
    "option1":"* (asterisk)",
    "option2":"| (pipeline)",
    "option3":"- (hyphen)",
    "option4":"_ (underscore)",
    "answer":"4"
},
    {
        "question":"How would you round off a value from 1.66 to 2.0?",
        "option1":"ceil(1.66)",
        "option2":"floor(1.66)",
        "option3":"roundup(1.66)",
        "option4":"roundto(1.66)",
        "answer":"1"
    },
    {
        "question":"By default a real number is treated as a",
        "option1":"float",
        "option2":"double",
        "option3":"long double",
        "option4":"far double",
        "answer":"2"
    },
    {
        "question":"When we mention the prototype of a function?",
        "option1":"Defining",
        "option2":"Declaring",
        "option3":"Prototyping",
        "option4":"Calling",
        "answer":"2"
    },{
        "question":"In which header file is the NULL macro defined?",
        "option1":"stdio.h",
        "option2":"stddef.h",
        "option3":"stdio.h and stddef.h",
        "option4":"math.h",
        "answer":"3"

    },{
        "question":"If a variable is a pointer to a structure, then which of the following operator is used to access data members of the structure through the pointer variable?",
        "option1":".",
        "option2":"&",
        "option3":"*",
        "option4":"->",
        "answer":"4"
    },
    {
        "question":"A pointer is",
        "option1":"A keyword used to create variables",
        "option2":"A variable that stores address of an instruction",
        "option3":"A variable that stores address of other variable",
        "option4":"All of the above",
        "answer":"3"
    },
    {
        "question":"The operator used to get value at address stored in a pointer variable is",
        "option1":"*",
        "option2":"&",
        "option3":"&&",
        "option4":"||",
        "answer":"1"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following function sets first n characters of a string to a given character?",
        "option1":"strinit()",
        "option2":"strnset()",
        "option3":"strset()",
        "option4":"strcset()",
        "answer":"2"

    }];
